Du hast erwähnt, dass Du viele Jahre Mitte-links gewählt hast. Wie blickst Du seit dem 7. Oktober auf Politik in Israel?
Center-left, always center-left.
I also had elections where I voted far left,
"Peace Now" and all those.
I used to be part of it.
I still wish...
you know, I had friends from there.
There are great people on the other side.
Some of them are really good people,
and I really hope that it will be...
we need to stop radical Islam.
Because Islam and
radical Islam are two different religions.
And we just need to stop the radical Islamism
around the Middle East, around this region.
I have a problem with the left and right,
because I think that the world has gone completely mad,
today, if you’re
right of Marx, you’re far right.
I think that people have to understand one thing:
Once...
Once survival is on the line,
all that philosophy is flushed down the drain.
When people
are aiming
weapons towards your children
and coming and slaughtering
so many of your friends...
So many of the Israelis changed their minds,
and we were even laughed at because we were
the stronghold of the left, they said:
"You see how naive you are",
"You gave them jobs you gave them ...",
So what it actually did was
make the left side in Israel less strong.
It’s a problem.
When you are dealing with a terror organization,
when you are fighting against guerrilla groups,
it’s completely different than what we are
used to.